ANUSHRUTI BAVASKAR

+91-7058442552 · bavaskaranushruti23@gmail.com · Pune, Maharashtra https://www.linkedin.com/in/anushruti-bavaskar/

PROFILE

A result-oriented individual with Master's in Computer Applications having 1+ years of experience, seeking a suitable position at a reputed organization where I can use my extensive knowledge in software design and development and further learn new things and grow as a Frontend Developer. Interested in devising a better problem-solving method for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools if the need arises.

SKILLS

React JS	HTML	WordPress
JavaScript	Css	PHP
Typescript	VS Code	MySql
C, C++	Drupal	MongoDB

WORK EXPERIENCE

Intelliswift Software Pvt. Ltd. Associate Software

July 2022 - June 2023

Accomplishments:

- · Worked well independently and on a team to solve problems.
- Developed and maintain the product along with reports making for management to make further decisions.
- · Handle multiple projects concurrently.
- Contributed to the creation of company objectives and worked to support them.
- Fully engaged with team members to achieve the highest levels of productivity.
- · Effectively multi-tasked and prioritized projects according to need.
- A few projects which I have delivered to clients are given below -

Project name: RMG - Talent Pool June 2022 - Jan 2023

Technologies: React Js Databases: MySql

Accomplishments:

- Actively contributed to all phases of software development life cycle, ensuring comprehensive engagement from project initiation to deployment.
- Proficient in writing well-designed, testable, and efficient code to meet project requirements and adhere to industry best practices
- In this project we use React JS technology and MySql database.
- This we got from Kotak bank which is known as Online Fire Brigade entries.
- Where you get any issues related to fire, by using this website you can raise you issues.

Project name: LMG - Website development & maintainance

Jan 2023 - April 2023

Technologies: Drupal, PHP

Databases: MySql

Accomplishments:

- Ensured project designs align with specified requirements, maintaining compliance with client expectations.
- Maintained website in well-mannered as per client requirement.
- Using some brands prepare there size charts, FAQs, Catelogues, etc.
- Working with Homecenter, Max, etc. types of brands to maintain there products online websites.

Project name: IDE - Internal Project May 2023 - June 2023

Technologies: ReactJS & ReactTS

Accomplishments:

- Implemented some ideas about for future coming projects.
- Develop some various types of components like- Buttons, Drop-downs, Tags, etc.
- Used React JS in the frontend to enhance the User Experience.

Campus Software (Internship)

March 2022 - May 2022

Accomplishments:

- Attended corporate learning and development programs to gain competencies and professional skills.
- Studied basic project requirements with assigned technical lead and planned development strategies.
- · Complete one project as a assignment are given below -

Online Food Ordering Website

Technologies: HTML, CSS, Javascript

Database : MySql

Accomplishments:

- Implemented the website as a assessment.
- · Working on frontend development.
- Develop whole website using HTML, Css and Javascript.

EDUCATION

Dr. D Y Patil Institute of Masters of Computer Application, Akurdi

Master of Computer Application(MCA) 2020 - 2022 (78.50 %)

Smt. P. K. Kotecha Mahila Mahavidyalaya, Bhusawal

Bachelor's of Computer Science(BSc) 2017 - 2020 (78.97 %)

CERTIFICATION

- Core Java Certification
- · React Js Certification

LANGUAGE KNOWN

- English
- Hindi
- Marathi